<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Max Kanter</title>
    <link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Max Kanter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jmaxkanter.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You cannot do data science without open source</title>
      <link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/open-source-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/open-source-data-science/</guid>
      <description>When I joined Alteryx last year, one of the first things I heard from our CEO Dean Stoeker was a quote inspired by the inventor Buckminster Fuller. It went along the lines of
 We are building all the right technologies for all the wrong reasons. We will not be able to operate Spaceship Earth very well nor for much longer unless we see it as a common cause. It has to be none of us or all of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/papers/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a selection of papers I have authored or co-authored
 The Machine Learning Bazaar: Harnessing the ML Ecosystem for Effective System Development pdf Deep Feature Synthesis: Towards Automating Data Science Endeavors pdf Prediction Factory: automated development and collaborative evaluation of predictive models pdf Label, Segment, Featurize: a cross domain framework for prediction engineering pdf CommunityFinder: Software to Analyze Communities that Develop in MOOC Discussion Forums pdf Activity Classification using Smartphone Accelerometer Data pdf ColorCrack: Identifying Cracks in Glass pdf OK: OAuth 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>