<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Max Kanter</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/</link><description>Recent content on Max Kanter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jmaxkanter.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analyzing Marathon Race Data</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/chicago-marathon-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/chicago-marathon-2022/</guid><description>To believe I can run a faster race by crunching numbers at my computer is probably nothing more than wishful thinking. Regardless, it was fun to explore this data, and I hope to present some novel ways of analyzing marathon race data.</description></item><item><title>Modeling the Economics of Residential Solar</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/solar-economics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/solar-economics/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed trying new technologies for as long as I can remember. In this post, I explore if installing solar panels on my home is worth it.</description></item><item><title>Reading Audiobooks</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/reading-audiobooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/reading-audiobooks/</guid><description>Unpacking the unspoken etiquette when saying you &lt;em>read an audiobook&lt;/em>.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Automated Feature Engineering to Feature Stores</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/beyond-automated-feature-engineering/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/beyond-automated-feature-engineering/</guid><description>While automating human intelligence is exciting, the core challenge is providing machine learning-ready data for developers who don&amp;rsquo;t want to do feature engineering.</description></item><item><title>Running in the wrong direction</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/wrong_direction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/wrong_direction/</guid><description>The last 7 years all kicked off because my curiosity lead me in the direction of a new technology and great group of people to work with. Now, it’s time to do that again by starting to running again, even if it might be in the wrong direction.</description></item><item><title>Leaving Alteryx</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/leaving-alteryx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/leaving-alteryx/</guid><description>After 2 years, last month marked the end of my time at Alteryx.</description></item><item><title>You cannot do data science without open source</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/open-source-data-science/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/posts/open-source-data-science/</guid><description>While I had a strong feeling back in 2017 when I made my first open source library, it’s even more clear today that you cannot do data science without open source.</description></item><item><title>Bookshelf</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/bookshelf/</guid><description>Here are some of the books I&amp;rsquo;ve read. I hope to add notes on what I took away from each soon. For now, I&amp;rsquo;ve stared the books I particularly enjoyed.
Do you have recommendations me? Let me know.
How We Got to Now by Steven John Lying by Sam Harris Outliers by Malcom Gladwell The Art of War by Sun Tzu High Output Management by Andy Grove Kite Runner by Khaled Hosseini ★ Skunk Works: A Personal Memoir by Ben Riche ★ Atomic Habits by James Clear ★ Surely You&amp;#39;re Joking, Mr.</description></item><item><title>Papers</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/papers/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a selection of papers I have authored or co-authored
The Machine Learning Bazaar: Harnessing the ML Ecosystem for Effective System Development pdf Deep Feature Synthesis: Towards Automating Data Science Endeavors pdf Prediction Factory: automated development and collaborative evaluation of predictive models pdf Label, Segment, Featurize: a cross domain framework for prediction engineering pdf CommunityFinder: Software to Analyze Communities that Develop in MOOC Discussion Forums pdf Activity Classification using Smartphone Accelerometer Data pdf ColorCrack: Identifying Cracks in Glass pdf OK: OAuth 2.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jmaxkanter.com/projects/</guid><description>Heat Pumps Work
I started looking into electrifying my house and learned about the effectiveness of electric heat pumps to heat and cool while fighting climate change. As I dug deeper, I realized there were a lot of calculations to determine if they were worthwhile that depended on local factors like the weather and price of energy. I built this site to help others determine if heat pumps will work for them.</description></item></channel></rss>